<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events on GopherCon 2015</title>
    <link>http://gophercon.com/events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events on GopherCon 2015</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 16:03:09 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://gophercon.com/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Official After Party</title>
      <link>http://gophercon.com/events/after-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 16:03:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gophercon.com/events/after-party/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;wynkoop-brewing-company:107e8e67e390571b792c0c88fa16d6e4&#34;&gt;Wynkoop Brewing Company&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;wednesday-july-8th-8-00pm-11-00pm:107e8e67e390571b792c0c88fa16d6e4&#34;&gt;Wednesday July 8th 8:00pm - 11:00pm&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This evening’s offsite event will once again take place at the Wynkoop Brewing Company, Colorado’s oldest brew pub. Back when now-Governor John Hickenlooper was just an out- of-work geologist, Denver law
prohibited the brewing and selling of beer in one establishment. Governor Hickenlooper decided to change this and opened Denver’s first craft brewery. The building he chose was originally Denver’s J.S. Mercantile building, built in 1899 and most impressive of its time. With hardwood floors, thick
timber pillars, and pressed tin ceilings, your guests will be just as fascinated with the architecture as they are the beer! The Wynkoop even hosted President Obama in July 2014, who joined Governor Hickenlooper in a friendly game of pool!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://gophercon.com/images/afterparty/wynkoop2.png&#34; align=&#34;left&#34; style=&#34;width: 200px; margin: 25px;&#34; class=&#34;img-rounded&#34;&gt;
Upon arrival, guests will enter the main level where a large bar and ample seating is available. Just beyond the bar, the Mercantile Room will host a special tasting area for the evening. For guests that want to learn more about Colorado’s local brewery explosion, four (4)
professional beer experts will be on-hand to answer questions on all
matters of beer, including brewing processes, storage, serving, and
sampling. Hops and grains such as wheat, barley and rye will be
displayed in glass containers, while tasting notes will allow guests to
have an interactive and hands-on experience under the guidance of our
brew experts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://gophercon.com/images/afterparty/wynkoop3.png&#34; align=&#34;right&#34; style=&#34;width: 150px; margin: 25px;&#34; class=&#34;img-rounded&#34;&gt;
Throughout the evening, groups of up to twenty guests at a time will be taken on tours to check out the behind-the-scenes action of the brewery! They will explore the Wynkoop’s brewing process and may even sample some of the most popular brews like Silverback Pale Ale, Wixa Weiss, and Rail Yard Ale. Additionally, beer stations throughout the brewery will provide ample opportunities for everyone to try some new beers, whether going on the tour or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://gophercon.com/images/afterparty/wynkoop4.png&#34; align=&#34;left&#34; style=&#34;width: 200px; margin: 25px;&#34; class=&#34;img-rounded&#34;&gt;
In addition to the main level, guests will have use of the Wynkoop’s entire second floor pool hall. This expansive space features a large bar, ample seating, dartboards, pool tables, table shuffleboard, and foosball. In this area, guests can visit with the Wynkoop’s resident pool shark, “The Viper”. Before her career exploded, Colorado native Melissa Little could be found
at the Wynkoop on a regular basis and even had her own designated table. She has been playing pool for over 25 years, is ranked 5th in the United States, and 17th in the world. Tonight Melissa will interact with guests while coordinating mini-challenges, demonstrating her skills in a trick shot show, and autographing cue balls for a few lucky attendees!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.wynkoop.com/&#34;&gt;Wynkoop Brewing Company&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1634 18th St.&lt;br /&gt;Denver, CO 80202&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>